imtiredonline.com 2012-06-27

# Privacy Policy | ITo Products

We are committed to protecting the privacy and security of your personal information.

This Privacy Policy describes the types of personal information we may collect, how we may use this information and when (under certain circumstances) we may disclose this information. This Privacy Policy also details the steps we have taken to secure your personal information. By visiting our Site, you accept the practices described in this Privacy Policy.

## INFORMATION COLLECTION

2CC/ITo will not collect any personal information about you except when specifically and knowingly provided by you. Examples of such information are name, shipping and billing addresses, phone number, email address, credit card information and customer preferences data. Examples of ways in which we may collect such information from you include the following:

** ** |  | A. | Registration and Ordering. Before using certain parts of this Site or ordering products, you must complete a registration form. When registering, you will be prompted to provide certain personal information, including but not limited to your name, shipping and billing addresses, phone number, email address, and credit card number. In addition, you may also be asked to provide your country of residence and/or your organization’s country of operation, so we can comply with applicable laws and regulations, and for your gender. These kinds of personal information are used for billing purposes, to fulfill your orders, to communicate with you about your order and this Site, and for internal marketing purposes. If we encounter a problem when processing your order, we will use the personal information to contact you.  
---|---  
B. | Email Addresses. Some areas of the site allow you to enter your email address for purposes including, but not limited to: registering for an ITo account.  
  
## INFORMATION USE

We do not sell or rent information about our customers and all information provided to 2CC/ITo remains absolutely confidential, except that:

** ** |  | A. | We may share information with companies that provide support services to us (such as a printer, mailing house, fulfillment company or web host) or that help us market our products and services. These companies may need information about you in order to perform their functions. These companies are not authorized to use the information we share with them for any other purpose.  
---|---  
B. | We will use your personal information to communicate with you about your orders and deliveries, and we may send you a confirmation email when you register/place an order with us. Also, if you submit your email address to signup for newsletters, blogs or to open a 2CC/ITo account, we use it to deliver the information to you.  
C. | We may be required to disclose such information in response to subpoenas, court orders, requests from law-enforcement officials, or if we are otherwise required to disclose such information by law.  
D. | We may publicly disclose the name, city, and state of the winner of any online sweepstakes.  
  
## PROTECTING YOUR INFORMATION

Shopping on the site is secure and worry-free. We have taken several measures to guarantee that your order and your credit card information are safe and secure. Our servers use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL), an advanced encryption technology that works with all major Internet browsers.

SSL is considered the industry standard and is among the leading software available to encrypt online transactions. Your personal information including your name, credit card number and address is encrypted so that it cannot be read as it is transmitted over the Internet. Regardless of these efforts, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Therefore, any information you transmit to us is sent at your own risk.

## CHILDREN’S PRIVACY

We do not intentionally collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. If we become aware that we have collected personally identifiable information from a user of the site who is under the age of thirteen, we will remove that child’s personal information from our files.

## OFFLINE COLLECTION, USE & DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION

The majority of information that we collect is obtained through our site, and this Privacy Policy applies only to that online collection of personal information. We also collect information offline, where we also try to protect the privacy of your personal information. One example involves someone calling us to place an order or to ask questions. When someone calls, we will ask only for the personal information we need in order to place the order or to answer the question.

## POLICY CHANGES

We may change our Privacy Policy from time-to-time. We encourage you to refer to this Privacy Policy on an ongoing basis so that you understand our current Privacy Policy.

## QUESTIONS AND FEEDBACK

We welcome your questions, comments and concerns about privacy. Please send us any and all feedback pertaining to privacy, or any other issue at [info@ImTiredOnline.com](mailto:info@ImTiredOnline.com).
